<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Life | Piao's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://messipiao.github.io/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://messipiao.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-14T20:17:10+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://messipiao.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Chen Piao]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[messipiao@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
    <link href="http://messipiao.github.io/blog/2013/10/30/hello-world/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-30T13:10:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://messipiao.github.io/blog/2013/10/30/hello-world</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello world, it’s Piao’s first post from his own lab.</p>

<p>I want to have my own blog for a long time and I have tried some blogs in China, like 163 blog or blogbus. However, neither of them satisfied me as there are some restrictions from the websites and they are not as neat as what I thought blogs should be. Luckily, with recommendations and help from Super P, I finally have this amazing blog! I will share what I’ve learned and felt here, as a record of my study and life in NUS.</p>

<p>I’ve been in NUS for 3 months. Actually, Sinapore is very much like China, no matter in food taste or language (you can just say Chinese in your normal life), so I feel like only from one city to another while less feeling of being abroad.</p>

<p>What makes happy is that I met my GF here. She is beautiful and kind and I am really grateful that I can have her with me here. Another thing is that I have a place in the lab, which I have dreamed for a long time. In the lab, I can concentrate on the study like a nut! It’s a great feeling.</p>

<p>Talk less and do more. I should work harder to have a bright future, for myself, my family and especially for my GF.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
